There was once a demon more terrifying
and evil than Demon King Ahriman.
If someone made him angry, humans, demons,
and entire countries would be
utterly destroyed.
He was considered an
unstoppable living calamity.
The previous demon king, known
as the King of Destruction...
His name is Zareth!
THE PREVIOUS DEMON KING IS TOO SCARY!!
"The Previous Demon King Is Too Scary!!"
My father, the previous demon king Zareth,
is about to celebrate
his 10,000th birthday...
Yes, Your Majesty!
My father was feared as
the King of Destruction.
If he comes here and
sees Doux like this...
Th-That would not be good, Your Majesty.
So you think so, too...
I'm terribly sorry!
You've left me in charge
of Lady Doux's education,
and yet, she still remains too kind.
Yes...
Doux is just too kind.
If all else fails, please
allow me to take her
on a special trial:
a demon social studies trip.
Demon social studies trip?
DEMON SOCIAL STUDIES TRIP
I will have Lady Doux
witness the atrocities of several
evil demons over several days.
Oho!
Then Lady Doux will be influenced
by the other demons' hearts
and shall awaken to her own evil heart.
A demon social studies trip?
I will have you learn what
exactly demons are on this trip.
This is a special trial just for that.
Special!
These are trapping specialists.
They are called goblins.
It is their job to capture the humans
that we use in the demon world.
Humans will be coming
through here soon.
Try capturing one, Lady Doux.
You can use any method you please,
but you should try beating them to
soften them up for capture.
It's fun.
Goblins are some of the cruelest
to humans out of all demons.
If she sees that, I'm sure the evil
heart within Lady Doux will awaken!
Here they come! Get 'em!
Hurt them!
I'm scared!
Yay!
I caught a human!
Er, good! Well done, Lady Doux.
Again! I wanna do that again!
Next, I'm gonna catch some goblins!
Huh?
Humans! Let's catch them together!
Wh-What are you talking about?
We don't have time to
waste on such nonsense!
A FEW MINUTES LATER
Catch them!
Run away! Run away!
Playing is more fun than beating!
They are black magicians.
Black maggie-shuns...?
They are demons who use magic
to create calamities and
illnesses to make humans suffer.
We were just about to cast
a spell on a nearby village.
We'll teach you a spell that will make
your hair stand on end, Lady Doux.
Yay!
Torturing humans with various spells
brings black magicians the utmost joy.
I'm sure if Lady Doux
sees that, she'll also...
Now, let us cast the spell.
A FEW MINUTES LATER
Jelly... beans?
No, no! This letter is "zue."
It's "Zuraibe Leusa."
You're so funny, Lady Doux!
It's gonna take her five days
to learn a single page.
But this might be more
fun than cursing people.
This is a death plant. They devour
humans down to their bones.
We feed humans who defy demons to them.
The death plants are
especially voracious today.
If she hears the pitiful
screams of the humans
being melted down to their
bones by a death plant,
I'm sure she'll...
A FEW MINUTES LATER
Hey! Stop playing around!
Your job is to eat humans!
Take that!
Yah!
Hup!
Take that and that!
Take that!
Yay! I hit them! I hit them!
That's it, Doux!
Yay!
Demons are supposed to be evil
and yet, they keep falling
to Lady Doux's pleasant nature.
I see...
So that's why you came to me.
Please...
You're the only one I can rely
on at this point, Lady Setia.
Goodness, how pathetic.
Are mermaids demons, too?
Mermaids are demons who lure
in sailors with their song.
We get to sing?!
Yes.
Humans whose hearts are
captivated by our song
willingly throw themselves into the sea
and sink to the bottom.
Big Sister Jahi!
Oh no! My mind's weakened, so I've
been affected by the cursed song...
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Oh? Looks like a ship has
shown up at the perfect time.
Now, come sing with me, Lady Doux.
Let's sing the cursed song.
Okay!
Hey!
What's going on?!
Hi!
Doux's song is so soothing for the soul.
Even Lady Setia...
Why does this always happen?!
Papa! I'm home!
Ah, you're back!
How many special trials did you do?
Seven!
I see, I see.
Well, Jahi? Has there
finally been some progress?
As I feared...
I have failed as Lady Doux's attendant.
We had her accompany various
demons performing heinous deeds,
but there has been no progress.
That's not true! I'm sure
Doux has changed as well.
Isn't that right, Doux? How
were the special trials?
What did you think of them?
Um, well...
I thought I wanted to be
more like the other demons!
Lady Doux!
Is that so, Doux?
Yeah!
Isn't that great, Jahi?
Yes!
All of my troubles until now
have finally become worth it.
Now I'll be able to face my father.
Because everyone was so nice!
Huh?
I want to take care of my
friends like the goblins...
The black maggie-shuns helped
me learn some new words...
I want to sing pretty
songs like the mermaids...
Then there's Big Sister Jahi
who's always really nice
and always with me as she
gives me trials to do...
Doux wants to be a demon
just like all of them!
I'm... nice?
Me...?
No, Doux... You've got it all wrong.
Pardon me, Your Majesty!
What is it?
Lord Zareth has arrived.
What?
But he wasn't supposed to arrive yet.
THE PREVIOUS DEMON KING IS TOO MUCH OF A DOTING GRANDPA!!
"The Previous Demon King Is Too
Much of a Doting Grandpa!!"
Father!
You should've told us that you were
arriving early so we could greet you.
No need.
It's been a while, Ahriman.
I hadn't been able to return to the
castle after hurting my back.
Nor have I been able to
advise you properly.
I apologize.
No, no, that's no problem at all.
It is a pleasure to meet you.
I am Jahi the attendant.
Thank you for coming all this way.
You must be tired from your long journey.
Allow me to show you to your room.
That can wait.
Huh?
More importantly... where's Doux?
D-Did you need to see
Doux for some reason?
I'm asking you where the
next demon king who has
strayed from the path to
becoming a proper demon is.
L-L-Lady Doux is in her room...
I have to hurry! I have to hurry!
The next demon king must not
be allowed to stray from the path
of becoming a proper demon.
Are her surroundings causing this?
Is it because you're both spoiling her?
I came here early to eradicate
whatever is getting in the way
of Doux becoming a proper demon.
That is my purpose!
Th-This is bad, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
Is this Doux's room?
P-Please wait, Lord Zareth!
F-Father, I'm sure that Doux must
need to mentally prepare herself.
So please go to the room we've
prepared for you for now...
You're hiding something, aren't you?!
Let me see her at once!
Ah! It's Pawpaw!
Pawpaw!
Doux! It's been too long!
You've gotten so big!
Come, let me hold you...
O-Oh no. I almost forgot why I came here.
That's right. If I spoil her as well,
Doux will never become a proper demon.
Pawpaw!
She will not be able to survive
this cruel demon world!
You must be the demon
that you are, Zareth.
You must be cruel to set
Doux on the right path!
I will find out what is hindering
Doux from becoming a proper demon
and eradicate it!
"HEY, PAWPAW"
LYRICS: KANATA NAKAMURA
COMPOSITION AND ARRANGEMENT: RYOTA TESHIMA
SONG: DOUX
Hey, hey, hey, Pawpaw
Look, look, the weather outside
Is just like how I feel
Mr. Sun is smiling
Because I get to be with Pawpaw
I wanna hold your hands
Can I hold your hands?
They're so cold yet so warm
My Pawpaw's hands
I see. So Doux starts off
her days with a walk.
She walks through nature,
picking up acorns, and
collecting fallen leaves...
This must be why she's
become such a kind child.
Wait, no!
Walks are unnecessary!
I was about to let Doux's
smile sway me yet again.
I'm accompanying Doux so I can set her
on the correct path away
from these peaceful habits!
Do not forget your mission, me!
Why haven't you realized that this walk
itself is causing Doux to be so kind?!
Make her stop at once!
B-But, but, Father...
Pawpaw!
I made you a bed, Pawpaw!
Take a nap here, Pawpaw.
S-So precious!
Doux!
Wait, no, no!
You must resist the temptation, me!
What is this place?
This is our quarry.
We make the enslaved humans work here.
Here!
Oh, thank you.
Er, Lady Doux! Why are you
suddenly helping people?!
Doux!
Oh, hey, everyone!
What should we play today?
She's having fun and smiling.
I was worried about her making friends,
but I guess that was unnecessary.
Humans and demons can see through
their differences and be friends...
Wait! She absolutely must
not be friends with humans!
You mustn't be like that, Doux!
This place will poison you.
Never step foot in it again.
But...
Understand?
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry, Doux!
Unnecessary! Unnecessary! Unnecessary!
That's also unnecessary!
This is all for your own sake!
Regarding your schedule for today,
we will begin the celebration
for you at ten in the great hall.
His Majesty will do his opening speech,
then the guests will say a few words,
followed by the executive members,
It's finally the day of
my birthday celebration.
and then we will have you say
a few words, Lord Zareth.
Thank goodness. I won't be able
to keep it together much longer.
Then we will head over
to the great dining hall
to give a toast
and then enjoy the banquet.
Once the festivities are
over, I'll go home at once...
Come in.
Good morning, Pawpaw.
Pawpaw, um...
Doux has something she
wants to show you today.
So please come to my room...
Have you been doing what
I've told you to do?
Not yet.
But, um...
Are you still going to
come up with excuses?
If you wish to speak with me,
you must do everything I've
ordered you to do first.
I have better things to do
than play house with you.
Let us go, Jahi.
Y-Yes, but...
What? Are you going to
talk back to me, as well?
L-Lady Doux!
Do not chase after her!
Let's go.
Yes, sir.
So that's Lord Zareth...
He's really intense.
It's killing everyone's appetite...
I heard that he'll kill
you if you make him angry.
Where's Doux?
Huh?! Well, um...
She hates me! Doux hates me!
Wait, why am I lamenting?
I was prepared for this to happen!
I am going to the bathroom.
Lord Zareth!
Leave me be.
This is how it should be.
So that she can cast aside her
kindness and survive as a demon...
I had to set Doux on the right path.
This is... Doux's room.
Doux?
HAPPY BIRTHDAY PAWPAW!!
Did you make all of this?
Yup...
I wanted to surprise you because
it's your birthday today, Pawpaw.
So I made this and didn't
even tell Papa or Big Sister Jahi.
But I'll make sure to
clean all this up, too...
I won't go on walks anymore
and I won't... go see
the humans as much...
So...
I wanna talk with you more, Pawpaw.
Doux!
It's okay! It's okay, Doux!
You can change at your own pace
without having anyone hold you down!
Please forgive me, Doux!
I... I was wrong.
I've never received a gift
that made me so happy before!
This goes here.
Like this?
Yup! I'll put one on you, too, Pawpaw!
Oh! Both of you, come help us!
We'll have the rest of my birthday
celebration in Doux's room!
Having a grandchild is wonderful!